A Guide to the Records of George Bernard Lorraine, ca. 1925-1976
Library of Virginia
- Real estate records (Box 1-149)
  - Virginia real estate (Box 1-146)
    - Hanover County (Box 46-54A)
      - Summer Hill: W.B. Newton, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - Sunnyside: S.P. Tignor, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - Sunnyside: Charles H. Beck, 1938-1961 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - Taylor's Creek: Louise Morris, 1937-1940 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Verdon: Mr. Redd, 1939 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Vergennes: Leslie de Vergennes Lavalle, 1942-1963 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Walnut Lane: G.R. Tener, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Warner Hall: 1940 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Williamsville: Wilson M. Brooks (realtor), 1936-1953 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Woodbury: J.W. Peace, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - Wonderland Nurseries: J.H. Thompson, 1956 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Wood Grove: W.R. Gardner, 1938-1940 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Woodland or Woodlawn: R.R. Carter, 1940-1941 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Ayers, R.W.: 27 acres, 1936-1940 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Bank, Mr.: 26 acres, 1930's (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Beadles, L.B.: 41 acres, 1937-1940 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Beasley, S.T.: 117 acres, 1952 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Bowe, Mr.: n.d. (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - Bradford, J.C.: 278 acres, 1940 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Campbell, Leslie: 100 acres, 1939-1940 (Box 52, Folder 17)
      - Carter brothers: 140 acres, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 18)
      - Cary, Miles B.: 1955 (Box 52, Folder 19)
      - Cox, Mr.: 1939 (Box 52, Folder 20)
      - Cross, E.C.: 117 acres, 1939-1940 (Box 52, Folder 21)
      - Daugherty, T.H.: 1963, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 22)
      - Dickinson, George F.: 1952 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Dillard, W.R.: 1953-1954 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Eaves, George W.: 200 acres, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Epps, Jack: 1953 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Fisher, Mrs.: 1937 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Fletcher, S.H.: Ditchley Park, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - Fortune, Gertrude N.: 161 acres, 1955-1961 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Fry, Mr.: 66 acres, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Green, W.J.: 90 acres, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Gregory, Mr.: 17 acres, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Hanover National Bank: 1935-1936 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Harris, V.C.: 205 acres, 1940 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Higgins, Dr.: 105 acres, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Houser, C.W.: 1947 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Jacobs, A.S.: 9 acres, 1936-1941 (Box 53, Folder 15)
      - Lewis, John Taylor: 1944 (Box 53, Folder 16)
      - Lewis, W.T.: 90 acres, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 17)
      - Lien, O.L.: 120 acres, 1939-1940 (Box 53, Folder 18)
      - Loving, B.P.: 13 acres, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 19)
      - McGhee, Mrs.: 75 acres, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 20)
      - McGlocklin, S.A.: 1947 (Box 53, Folder 21)
      - Martin, J.D.: 1945 (Box 53, Folder 22)
      - Miner, Frank: 190 acres, 1952-1954 (Box 53, Folder 23)
      - Moody, Mr.: store, 1948 (Box 53, Folder 24)
      - Osbelt, Mr. (realtor): 109 acres, 1935 (Box 53, Folder 25)
      - Osbelt, Mr. (realtor): 30 acres, 1936 (Box 53, Folder 26)
      - Patterson, R.M.: 1953 (Box 53, Folder 27)
      - Payne, D.W.: 205 acres, 1946 (Box 53, Folder 28)
      - Pfeiffer, Jacqueline Steinke: Ditchley Park, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 29)
      - Powell, Leslie: 1934 (Box 53, Folder 30)
      - Powell, T.C.: 8 acres, 1945 (Box 53, Folder 31)
      - Reid, C.I.: n.d. (Box 53, Folder 32)
      - Richardson, C.M.: 12 acres, 1962, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Schulze, E.A.: 50 acres, 1935 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Simpkin, Mr.: 50 acres, 1934 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Smith, J.A.: 120 acres, 1936-1940 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Stone, M.T.: service station, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Waldrop, R.G.: 1954 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Wallinger, C.H.: 225 acres, 1941 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - White, Mrs.: 1949 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Wickham, J. Stuart: 1955 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Woolfolk, Jourdan: 3 acres, 1938 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Woolfolk, Jourdan: 130 acres, 1940 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Woolfolk, Jourdan: 1944-1954 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Woolfolk, Jourdan: 2 family flat, 1945-1953 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Woolfolk, Jourdan: 1946 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Woolfolk, Jourdan: store, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Woolfolk, Jourdan: 2 homes, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - Woolfolk, Jourdan: apartment, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - Woolfolk, Jourdan: bank and home, 1953 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1975 (Box 54A, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 54A, Folder 2-3)
    - Henrico County (Box 55-57)
      - Creighton: Henry Harrison Christian, 1942 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Curles Neck: Charles B. Ruddock, 1930-1942 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - Edgewood: A.B. Cromwell, 1943 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - Ethelwood: George S. Hewitt, 1937-1949 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - Glenbrooke Hills: William C. Carr, 1936 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - Glendale Farm: G.T. Fontaine, 1937-1939 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - Green Knoll: Greenhan Johnston, 1941-1948 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - Herndon: 36 acres, 1934 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - Loving Stone Farm: James A. Loving, 1942 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Malvern Hill: W.H. Ferguson, 1937-1942 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Mayfield Farm: N.T. Mosby, 1947 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Meadowview: Horace M. Clay, 1942 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - Myers Club: 4 acres, 1938 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - Oak Lawn: Irving Adams, 1953 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - Overlook: Carrie M. Smith, 1931 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Pollard Farm: W.B. Childney, 1935 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Runymeade Farm: Edward S. Schmidt, 1938 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Sailors Tavern: H. Carl Boschen, 1936 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - Southworth Farm: R.V. Southworth, 1936 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Turkey Island Estate: R.S. Christian, 1938 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - Walkerton Inn: Erasmus Guy Hopkins, 1941 (Box 55, Folder 21)
      - Walnut Hill Farm: Stephen and Frank D. Beveridge, 1940 (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - Williams Farm: D.E. Walker, 1936 (Box 55, Folder 23)
      - Wilton Farm: Bank of Commerce and Trust, 1933-1947 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - Anderson, Christ: 65 acres, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Baughan, H.R.: 61 acres, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Bentley, W.C.: 60 acres, 1935-1936 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Bollinger, R.L.: 239 acres, 1942 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Brauer, Walter R.: 117 acres, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Burton, D.D.: 7 1/2 acres, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Clay, Garland P.: 2 acres, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Forbes, Allen B.: 280 acres, 1945 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - Frayser, L.P.: 383 acres, 1946 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Hart, Herbert: 63 acres, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Hazard, C. Frank: 11 acres, 1950 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Jenkins, Mr.: 5 acres, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Jones, D.P.: 50 acres, 1942 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - King, Billy: 24 acres, 1947 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - McAnally, Dr.: 3 acres, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Martin, H.F.: 3 1/2 acres, 1960 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Miller, Craig: 1954-1955 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Nelson, Mr.: 86 acres, 1937 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Olmstead, Gerald: 8 acres, 1945 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - Putney, Langhorn: 34 acres, 1941 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Rennie, C. Bruce: 7 acres, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Rennie, C. Bruce: 8 acres, 1938 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Richeson, Frank S.: 26 acres, 1940-1942 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Roberts, H.K.: 27 acres, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 25)
      - Schertle, J.H.: 2 acres, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Smith, E.M.: 30 acres, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Stein, Mr.: 120 acres, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Stone, C.M.: 1950 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Wegner, C.G.: 48 acres, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Wingfield, H. Mason: 2 1/4 acres, 1939 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Young, Judge: 2 acres, 1955 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Unidentified residence: 20 acres, 1938 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1932-1959 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Henry County (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Highland County (Box 57, Folder 12-15)
      - Lazy K Ranch: R.C. Kendrick, 1950-1955 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Graves, J.H., Jr.: 237 acres, 1960 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - Miller, Mr.: 1442 acres, 1944-1946 (Box 57, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (empty) (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Isle of Wight County (Box 57-58)
      - Berryman Home: M.H. Overman, 1940-1946 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Carson Farm: C.T. Hutcheson, 1937-1940 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Fort Boykin: W.R. Weaver, 1935-1945 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Rainbow Farm: Mr. Luhring, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Rocks on James: Dale E. Snyder, 1936-1944 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Watkins Farm: John I. Cofer, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Bloxom, O.A.: 1954 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1940 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - James City County (Box 58-59)
      - Amblers on James: Jeanette H. Dimmick, 1937-1943 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Kingsmill Plantation: Thomas M. Brooks, 1953 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Lombardy: Branch Martin, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Powhatan: E.M. Slauson, 1954 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Powhatan: David J. Hayes, 1966-1967 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Riverview: H.L. Bloomberg, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Riverview: Mrs. McCourtney, 1951-1953 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Riverview: Ernest W. Goodrich, 1961 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Roseland Dairy Farm: B.F. Atkinson (realtor), 1957 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Temple Hall: B.T. Wortham, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Tory Point: Robert B. Colvin, 1958 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Waverly: Branch Martin, 1942 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Windsor Castle: Martha M. Ware, 1946-1960 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Brooks, Gardner T.: 300 acres, 1946 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Brouwers, J.B.: 5 acres, 1953-1954 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Cocke, Duncan: 7 acres, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Daub, K.B.: 1953 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Dennis, Thomas E.: 130 acres, 1939-1940 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Dryden, O.B.: 98 acres, 1952 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Faulkner, Clifford C.: 9 acres, 1956 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Hinchman, E.: 1946 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Hoar, Philip: 17 acres, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Honeycutt, Lige: 4 acres, 1957 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Jennings, B.N.: 1958 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Kilby, E.B.: 1 1/2 acres, 1955-1956 (Box 59, Folder 13)
      - McCartney, H.G.: 78 acres, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 14)
      - Meadows, Eugene R.: 700 acres, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 15)
      - Peninsula Bank and Trust Company: 30 acres, 1933-1941 (Box 59, Folder 16)
      - Taylor, R. Kemper, Jr.: 1955 (Box 59, Folder 17)
      - Van Rensselear, Mrs.: 1947 (Box 59, Folder 18)
      - Viatch, Philip: 1954 (Box 59, Folder 19)
      - Whitehead, John: 24 acres, 1953 (Box 59, Folder 20)
      - Unidentified Toano hotel: 1946 (Box 59, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1938 (Box 59, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1934-1961 (Box 59, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - King and Queen County (Box 60-61)
      - Aberdeen: L.C. Watkins, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Airville: H.P. Vaughan, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Bellview: Beverly R. Anderson, 1934-1943 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Brookshire: Andrew B. Brooks, 1944-1946 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Bewdley: Gordon Smith, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Dixon Hall: M.F. Portlock, Jr., 1936-1951 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Dudley's Ferry: J.C. Whaley, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Erin: M.M. Sutherland, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Forge: C.E. Edwards, 1941 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Ghost House: Mr. Van Landingham, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Glenwood: Margaret S. Webb, 1934-1936 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Green Mount: J.W. Fleet, 1942-1943 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Hockley: Mr. Elliott, 1944 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Hockley Farm: J.B. Gray, 1944-1945 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - Holly Hill: R.B. Fauntleroy, 1934-1945 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Melrose: J.S. Turner, 1934-1940 (Box 60, Folder 16)
      - Newington: W.G. Beane, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 17)
      - Orange Grove: W.E. Thrift & Company, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 18)
      - Peach Grove: A.Y. Masters, 1969 (Box 60, Folder 19)
      - Plain Dealing: John M. Dew, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 20)
      - Traveler's Rest: Clarence H. Martin, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 21)
      - Tudor Hall: J.R. Kidd, 1941 (Box 60, Folder 22)
      - White Hall: George Babyak, 1937-1943 (Box 60, Folder 23)
      - Benschoten, R.C.: 20 acres, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 24)
      - Bland, J.R.: 20 acres, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 25)
      - Daniels, T.S. (realtor): 100 acres, 1940 (Box 60, Folder 26)
      - Fauntleroy, Mrs.: 776 acres, 1941 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Sutton, J.H.: 130 acres, 1947 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1933-1945, 1951, 1972 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - King George County (Box 61-63)
      - Alto: Helen and John L. Jeffries, 1941 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Arcadia: H.G. Bullwinkel, 1953-1954 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Belle Grove Plantation: Mr. Hooker, 1930's (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Belle Isle: Richard H. Richards, 1955-1957 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Berkeley Hotel: M.E. Gutridge, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Berry Plain: Webster Grymes, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Bleak Hill: H.I Brock, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Cedar Grove Farm: Robert S. Nash, 1956 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Cettwood: Roger Lee Kenvin, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Clive: J. Armistead Lewis, 1948-1950 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Cleydarl: G.D. Richardson, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Cloverdale: A.A. Peed, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Echo Dill: J.W. Baldwin, 1967 (Box 61, Folder 17)
      - Freidland: B.A. Woolfolk, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 18)
      - King George Motel: C.L. Morrow, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 19)
      - Liberty: J.B. Cralle, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 20)
      - Marmion: R. Carter Grymes, 1944 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Merrilea: Janet M. Brown, 1951-1955 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Mount Lebanon: Mr. Nilsson, 1960 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Mount Stuart: Otto Williams, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Mount Stuart: Charles E. Daniels, 1954-1955 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Office Hall: T.S. Marshall, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Old Woodlown: Brant F. Elliott, 1931-1933 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Rokeby Farm: 315 acres, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Shelbourne Plantation: 100 acres, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Springhill: Harry S. Hall, 1943 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Walsingham: Mr. Parker (realtor), 1960 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - White Hall: Lucy Mullin, 1937-1941 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - White Plains: A.W. Walker, 1945-1959 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - White Plains: S. Schwoernthal, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Windsor Farm: N.E. Peed, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - Woodlawn: Emory T. Wales, 1947-1950 (Box 62, Folder 16)
      - Woodstock: Robert Sharp, 1952 (Box 62, Folder 17)
      - Boothe, W.R.: 1960 (Box 62, Folder 18)
      - Bundick, Clarkson U.: 72 acres, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 19)
      - Downham, George P.: 15 acres, 1946 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Franklin, B.F.: 150 acres, 1962 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Gibb, John W.: 241 acres, 1958 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Lewis, S.L.: 1959 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Morland, Mr.: 156 acres, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Nilsson, Mr.: 419 acres, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Stallings, V.V.: 1 3/4 acres, 1956 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Stallings, V.V.: 2 acres, 1960-1961 (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Staples, N.W.: 136 acres, 1934 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Van Aken, George W.: 25 acres, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Williams, A.L.: 1937-1938 (Box 63, Folder 11)
      - Williams, George D.: 50 acres, 1947 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Willis, Henry: 1955 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - Unidentifed property: 150 acres, 1943 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous letter file: 1931-1937 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - King William County (Box 63-65)
      - Bear Garden: Mrs. Flickeinger, 1938-1939 (Box 63, Folder 17)
      - Bleak Hill Farm: 1720 acres, 1952-1957 (Box 63, Folder 18)
      - Brick House Landing Farm: Walter E. Ruprecht, 1943-1953 (Box 63, Folder 19)
      - Brick House Landing: Mrs. Betoney, 1960 (Box 63, Folder 20)
      - Chelsea: John Blackwell, correspondence, 1954-1957 (Box 63, Folder 21)
      - Chelsea: photographs, 1954-1957 (Box 63, Folder 22)
      - Clarkfield: John L. Clark, 1942-1943 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Dunluce: Parker N. Little, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Edge Hill: J.E. Moren, 1943 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Edge Hill: G. Robert Leslie, 1946 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Edge Hill: Ellis Barley, 1946-1947 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Elsing Green: Roger T. Gregory, 1932-1933 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Elsing Green: Beverly Douglas Causey, 1947-1950, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Erlhaven: Bob Harrison, 1948-1950 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Ferry Farm: Adolph G. Prochazka, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Hollyfield Farm: John L. Clark, 1944-1952, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Horn Quarter: Edward E. Rowell, 1938 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Hybla Farm: T.H. Garnett, 1942-1945 (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Marl Hill: Travis Freeman Epes, 1940 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Marl Hill Farm: J.E. Brown, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Mount Columbia: J. Calvitt Clark, 1939-1942 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - North Point: J.N. Atkins, 1938-1941 (Box 64, Folder 16)
      - North Point: John C. Moore, 1961-1963 (Box 64, Folder 17)
      - Old Town: Mr. Garnett, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 18)
      - Piping Tree Farm: Nannie Haw Studley, 1940 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Pleasant Green: Juin Spiller, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Retreat: H.T. Louthan, 1936-1949 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Retreat: J.C. Myers, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - River Hill Farm: B.P. McGeorge, 1942 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Seven Springs: D.M. Barnett, 1945-1954 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Seven Springs: Doug Fleet, 1959-1960 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Shooting Box: Helen J. Sandlass, 1938-1946 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Union Farm: B.C. Slater, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Warsaw: L.L. McIntire, 1954-1955 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - West Point Dairy and Frozen Foods: R.C. Beuschorten, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - West Point Hotel: 1946 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Windsor Shade: J.D. Crockett, 1953-1957 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Windsor Shade: Francis W. Welch, 1932-1936 (Box 65, Folder 14)
      - Windsor Shades: W.C. Stone, 1953-1955 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      - Davis, Albert E.: 305 acres, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 16)
      - Gwathney, Mary Burnley: 1958-1959 (Box 65, Folder 17)
      - Heisey, Martha S.: 612 acres, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 18)
      - Lindenmeyer, C.E.: 1958 (Box 65, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous real estate listings (Box 65, Folder 20)
      - Historic Virginia Building Survey Information Blanks, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Lancaster County (Box 66-74)
      - 1 Apple Grove Farm: Hulbert E. Flowers, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Bald Eagle Cove: F.C. Haislip, 1946, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Barton Farm: J.S. Bromley, 1943 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Bay Hall: John Bullard, 1956-1957 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Belle Isle: J. Ray Callis, 1937-1940 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Belmont: R.O. Norris, Jr., 1937-1942 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Belmont: Dixon Foster, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Black Stump: Robert C. Carden, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Blakenore Pond: J. Edward Blakenore, 1941-1942 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Blue Water: W.S. Bryant, 1943-1945 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Bolling Hall: Dwight File, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Brandonlea: Charles B. Lee, 1939 (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Cow Shed: Nellie Leach, 1944-1950 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Enon Hall: Mr. McKesson, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Enon Hall Farm: Melvin C. Mass, 1945-1952 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Epping Forest: James D. Jessie, 1958-1960 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Farmville: Marjorie S. Eastwick, 1935-1948 (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Goodestone: Walter L. Goodwin, 1939 (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Greenfields: W. Collin Chilton, 1936-1937 (Box 66, Folder 19)
      - Greenvale: Chesapeake Banking Company, 1935-1942 (Box 66, Folder 20)
      - Hale Pontiac Building: Mr. Hale, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Hayden Hall: Olivia B. Hill, 1956-1960 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Homewood: Aldrich Dudley, 1936-1942 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - India Creek Farm: E.B. Richards, 1946 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Irvington Beach Hotel: 1949 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Kendall Hall: C.B. Levey, 1943-1946 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Hotel Kilmarnock: Enid Turner, 1945 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Hotel Kilmarnock: 1963 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - King Carter Inn: Elizabeth Springer Harrison, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Laurel Point: 1963-1965 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Level Fields: W.R. Smith, 1946-1959 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Long Lane: Mr. Herndon, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Melrose: Milton Webb, 1947 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Merry Point: W. Collin Chilton, 1935-1936 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Merry Point: H. Ledyard Towle, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Midway: Charles G. Snead, 1935-1958 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Midway: 1964 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Monaskon: M.L. Buckingham, 1948 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Monaskon: James A. Tarhutton, 1954-1960 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Monaskon: Russell Hayden, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Mosquito Point: Todd Wool, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - Oakley: Beaman Story, 1950 (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - Ocran Farm: Lloyd Squires, 1958-1959 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Old Blakemore Farm: George H. Stewart, 1945-1951 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Old Crawford: William M. Crawford, 1937-1956 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Old House Point: Mary Nash Goodwin, 1948 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Old House Point: Mr. Murdoch, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Pagan Point: Horace Reynolds, 1938-1944 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Pop's Castle: E.J. Lemmon, 1956-1959 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Prospect Hill: Thomas O'Sullivan, 1949 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Pop's Castle: Leonard Snider, 1935-1942 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Redwood House: C.F. Stevens, 1957-1958 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Ridgefield Farm: C.C. Wheat, 1942-1943 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Riverview: W.P. Thurston, 1932-1942 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Riverview Farm: W. Lucius Sanders, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Riverview Landing: John Garland Pollard, 1951-1953 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Riverview Landing: 1951-1962 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Spring Hill Farm: Paul B. Valle, 1960-1961 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Sterling Farm: Albert Shaw, Jr., 1952 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Sunnyside: 1965 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Towles Point: W.C. Towles, 1958-1962 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Turner Fruit Orchard: T.E. Turner, 1944-1945 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Verville: Horace Currie, 1956-1959 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Verville: Walter Oliver, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Verville: Walter Oliver, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Waterview Farm: B.N. Hubbard, 1938-1942 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Waterview Farm: W.M. Crawford (realtor), 1946 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - White Hall: Gilliam Haden, 1961 (Box 69, Folder 11)